How?
Announced!
In Bath!
That's fantastic!
What for?
Please suspend our business, don't shout on Zoom.
Bunch was VR, smooth, and Bennett's on Zoom.
D.M.
went dancing, soundbites, notes on our merch.
I did some boats, got paid to do the work.
You're saying words, hypocrites are making rent.
For my boy Graham's got a dance floor set.
So here's our truth, like Janet Smith.
Did so out, we're just funny, call it!
Which the thirds have swamped me, and we got better than some ghetto extreme offbeat.
Why?
You flippin' off the system, firing at it by the rage, cause I don't like supprism.
I still ain't the man, I just ain't workin' monthly.
My pants are t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t
The bear on the house, and he transpired You'll meet the lab rat, corporate hack So Scott LLC's in union back, since API phones are filing Didn't show out, we just bought it You bought it, just talking on rebellion Back with a bunch of dynoplastic, you're in hell, you bought it You made for Venus Gorgon, got sold free, but bought a pump for a fortune
Yo, I still hate cops, but I'm the H.O.
President now.
My backyard pumped fast in a ton, so you know I'm not sell-out.
It's my second fridge.
One for our milk, one for H. We bought it!
And yeah, shit don't fail!
Spring the truth just for jowl, and we bought it!
Go fast, get the frame, beat the steam bell!
We bought it!
Bought it with a patent, and man, fuck it was it!
Bought it, before patented, sell-out, we're just bought it!
So cute, nor Kate Jorson, nor St.
Brick Cloud.
Tid and John sell out.
Beasts might get their studies.
How about Bermuda?
Taiwan.